{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244357318","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244357316"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" b4635a9e-2f0b-4189-b62e-781767d4f33f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244368926","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244368926"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244372860","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244372860"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244380836","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244380836"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244390550","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244390550"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244398810","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244398810"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244409365","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244409365"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244412304","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244412304"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244414500","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244414500"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244416737","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244416737"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244426520","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244426520"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244428681","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244428681"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244430777","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244430776"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244433735","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244433735"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244435935","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244435935"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244438202","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244438202"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244441209","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244441208"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244443550","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244443550"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244445885","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244445885"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244448947","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244448947"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244451056","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244451056"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244453141","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244453141"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244456300","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244456300"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244458466","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244458466"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244460636","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244460636"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244463784","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244463784"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244466180","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244466180"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244476297","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244476296"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244479487","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244479486"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244481785","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244481785"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244484030","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244484030"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244488337","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244488336"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244495200","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244495200"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244501621","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244501620"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244505390","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244505390"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244507732","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244507732"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244510077","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244510077"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244519565","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244519565"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244521999","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244521999"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244528561","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244528561"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244537450","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244537450"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244541790","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244541790"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244544084","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244544084"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244547365","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244547365"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244549597","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244549597"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244551862","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244551862"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244555165","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244555165"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244557607","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244557607"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244560051","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244560051"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244562885","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244562884"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244565078","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244565077"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244567252","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244567252"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244570666","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244570666"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244573023","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244573023"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244575365","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244575365"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244578466","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244578465"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244580727","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244580727"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244583002","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244583002"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244586083","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244586082"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244588203","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244588202"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244590345","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244590344"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244602979","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244602979"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244608511","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244608510"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244610795","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244610795"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244614020","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244614020"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244622622","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244622621"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244624921","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244624920"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244630079","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244630079"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244632446","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244632446"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244634763","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244634762"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244637900","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244637900"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244640257","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244640257"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244642584","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244642584"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244646005","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244646005"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244646191","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244646191"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" fbbfc86c-b1e6-4824-a373-dfcc038040c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244657953","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244657953"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 008ea0a2-f56c-46a2-a2fb-fc95f86c8121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244658192","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244658192"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 008ea0a2-f56c-46a2-a2fb-fc95f86c8121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244659156","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244659156"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 008ea0a2-f56c-46a2-a2fb-fc95f86c8121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244660441","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244660440"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 008ea0a2-f56c-46a2-a2fb-fc95f86c8121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244663369","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244663368"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 008ea0a2-f56c-46a2-a2fb-fc95f86c8121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244664212","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244664212"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 008ea0a2-f56c-46a2-a2fb-fc95f86c8121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244664525","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244664525"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 008ea0a2-f56c-46a2-a2fb-fc95f86c8121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244665760","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244665760"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 008ea0a2-f56c-46a2-a2fb-fc95f86c8121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244669302","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244669302"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 008ea0a2-f56c-46a2-a2fb-fc95f86c8121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244670285","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244670285"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 008ea0a2-f56c-46a2-a2fb-fc95f86c8121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244670541","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244670540"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 008ea0a2-f56c-46a2-a2fb-fc95f86c8121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244671485","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244671485"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 008ea0a2-f56c-46a2-a2fb-fc95f86c8121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244674342","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244674341"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 008ea0a2-f56c-46a2-a2fb-fc95f86c8121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244675379","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244675378"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 008ea0a2-f56c-46a2-a2fb-fc95f86c8121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244675853","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244675853"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 008ea0a2-f56c-46a2-a2fb-fc95f86c8121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244680384","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244680383"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 008ea0a2-f56c-46a2-a2fb-fc95f86c8121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244680541","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244680541"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 008ea0a2-f56c-46a2-a2fb-fc95f86c8121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244694162","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244694162"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244697845","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244697845"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244699420","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244699419"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244701107","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244701107"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244702715","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244702715"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244705307","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244705307"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244706915","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244706914"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" polisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244711816","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244711816"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" polisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244713480","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244713479"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" parachichi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244723490","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244723490"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" parachichi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" START_PARACHICHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244724643","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244724643"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" parachichi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244726305","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244726305"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" papai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" PAPAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244728594","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244728594"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" papai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" PAPAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244730226","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244730226"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244732589","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244732589"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244734215","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244734215"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244743937","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244743936"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244745519","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244745519"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pilipili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" PILIPILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244756911","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244756911"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pilipili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244758507","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244758506"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244781707","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244781707"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244783285","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244783284"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" PERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244794605","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244794605"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" PERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244796169","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244796169"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" PUNDAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244799295","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244799294"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" PUNDAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244801301","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244801300"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244801507","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244801507"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 11402598-7b01-4f21-a5b6-f132d9ba0df4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" PUNDAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244814711","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244814710"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 0a099c2e-0acf-4b37-849a-53d9f468ffa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244817118","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244817118"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 0a099c2e-0acf-4b37-849a-53d9f468ffa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244818725","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244818725"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 0a099c2e-0acf-4b37-849a-53d9f468ffa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244820971","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244820971"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 0a099c2e-0acf-4b37-849a-53d9f468ffa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244822556","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244822556"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 0a099c2e-0acf-4b37-849a-53d9f468ffa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244827377","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244827377"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 0a099c2e-0acf-4b37-849a-53d9f468ffa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244828923","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244828923"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 0a099c2e-0acf-4b37-849a-53d9f468ffa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" polisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244833093","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244833093"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 0a099c2e-0acf-4b37-849a-53d9f468ffa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" polisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" START_POLISI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244834226","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244834226"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 0a099c2e-0acf-4b37-849a-53d9f468ffa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" polisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244835781","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244835781"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 0a099c2e-0acf-4b37-849a-53d9f468ffa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" parachichi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244837030","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244837030"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 0a099c2e-0acf-4b37-849a-53d9f468ffa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" parachichi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244837180","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244837180"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 0a099c2e-0acf-4b37-849a-53d9f468ffa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" parachichi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550244854188","data":{"timestamp":" 1550244854187"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_182438"," gameId":" 0a099c2e-0acf-4b37-849a-53d9f468ffa9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.55"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" parachichi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}